With everything going on right now, you ran for president, then you've just been MIA and people are like, that's fine because she needs to rest.
Black women need to rest.
And now here, when we are seeing incredible cuts to Medicaid and Medicare, when we are seeing all these people losing their jobs, when we're seeing that job growth in the United States has not only stalled but is on the descent, when we see that 30-year-olds in the United States cannot own their homes,
when we see this continued push for multiple streams of income, you should not need multiple streams of income to live.
She comes out with a book.
They are stripping people off of the streets in her state.
This was a time when she could have come back as a public servant and not as a politician that she has been for the duration of her career.
And it's not to say that politicians are not sometimes willing to listen to the work of organizers.
And yes, they do have to do that sometimes because they can't just completely 100% ignore, but they get so much support for just doing that little pittance.
We need public servants, not politicians.
There is an entire genocide that she was an accomplice to that has now gotten to such a fever pitch that we are seeing starvation every single day,
that the entire world, aside from maybe a few handful of nations, are now agreeing is a wrap.
This is a problem.
This has gotten too far.
And you put out a book?
This was the time?
Amen.